[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
♪ ♪
♪♪
[whistling melody]
[口哨旋律]
[grunts]
Special delivery!
[咕哝]
特别发货！
Ooh, my new rock
is finally here!
哦，我的新摇滚
终于来了！
Hold on, polka dots?
等等，波尔卡圆点？
I ordered plaid.
我订的是格子。
You'll have to take it back,
Mr. Mailman.
你必须把它拿回来
邮递员先生。
[bones cracking]
- Back?
[骨头碎裂]
- 回来？
- Mr. Mailman?
- My back.
- 邮递员先生？
- 我的背。
- You okay, buddy?
- Gotta deliver mail.
- 你还好吗，伙计？
- 必须递送邮件。
You are in no shape
to deliver anything, fella.
你没有任何形状
交付任何东西，伙计。
Just relax
and crash at my place.
放松一下
并在我的地方坠毁。
I'll deliver your mail
for you today.
我会递送你的邮件
今天给你。
Oops, almost forgot my mail bag.
哎呀，差点忘了我的邮袋。
Oops, almost forgot
my mailman hat.
哎呀差点忘了
我的邮递员帽子。
[humming melody]
All righty.
[哼唱的旋律]
好吧。
Let's see
where my first delivery is.
让我们看看
我的第一次送货是在哪里。
[straining]
[紧张]
Oh, I can't read this!
哦，我看不懂这个！
[knocks]
[敲门声]
Hey, Patrick, I thought
that sounded like your head.
嘿，帕特里克，我想
听起来就像你的头。
SpongeBob,
do you know where this
海绵宝宝，
你知道这个在哪里吗
Spon-gee-Boob
海绵布布
Squir-pa-Nants lives?
斯奎尔帕南特还活着吗？
- Never heard of him.
- Oh, well, return to sender.
- 从没听说过他。
- 哦，好吧，返回发件人。
Hey, what's with
the new threads?
嘿，怎么了
新线程？
I'm a mailman now!
[laughs]
我现在是一名邮递员了！
[笑]
Wow!
哇！
I've always wanted
to be a mailman.
我一直想要
成为一名邮递员。
It's like getting to be Santa
every day,
就像成为圣诞老人一样
每天，
except Sundays.
周日除外。
Sorry, SpongeBob,
but I'm the mailman now.
对不起，海绵宝宝，
但我现在是邮递员。
Oh, okay.
哦好的。
But you can be my postal pal!
但你可以成为我的邮友！
Whee!
Oh, ah!
哎哟！
哦，啊！
Let's get mailing.
我们去邮寄吧。
♪ ♪
♪♪
Postal pal,
you may ring the doorbell.
邮政朋友，
你可以按门铃。
[gasps]
[喘气]
Yes, sir, Mr. Mailman, sir.
是的，先生，邮差先生，先生。
Oh, I better warm up
the old bell ringer.
哦，我最好热身一下
老敲钟人
Up, down, up, down.
Twist right, twist left.
上，下，上，下。
向右扭转，向左扭转。
And polish the nail.
并擦亮指甲。
[exhales]
[呼气]
[doorbell rings]
[门铃响]
Mail!
邮件！
They let a moron like you
deliver the mail?
他们让像你这样的白痴
递送邮件？
Oh, you'd be surprised
what they let morons do.
哦，你会感到惊讶的
他们让白痴做什么。
[gasps]
[喘气]
It's here!
[laughs]
就在这里！
[笑]
What's wrong
with Squidward's face?
怎么了
带着章鱼哥的脸？
[laughing]
[笑]
I think he's smiling.
我认为他在微笑。
I finally got it,
my turbo clarinet.
我终于明白了
我的涡轮单簧管。
[engine rumbles]
[发动机隆隆声]
[inhales deeply]
[深吸一口气]
[horn toots]
- Whoa!
[喇叭嘟嘟]
- 哇！
[both screaming]
[两人尖叫]
Worth every penny.
每一分钱都值得。
[together]
Oh, ooh, oh, oh.
[一起]
哦，哦，哦，哦。
Oh, good, our next stop.
噢，很好，我们的下一站。
A summons for jury duty. Lucky.
担任陪审员的传票。幸运的。
Special delivery.
特别送货。
- Great job, Mr. Mailman.
- Huh?
- 干得好，邮差先生。
- 啊？
Oops.
哎呀。
Yep.
是的。
Ugh.
啊。
Must be a defective mail slot.
肯定是邮件槽有缺陷。
Aha.
啊哈。
That ought to do it.
应该可以做到这一点。
Maybe I'll
just try the doorbell.
也许我会
试试门铃。
[doorbell rings]
[门铃响]
Can I help you?
我可以帮你吗？
[together]
Special delivery.
[一起]
特别送货。
I don't want it!
我不想要它！
Maybe we should just move on
to the next house.
也许我们应该继续前进
到下一个房子。
Pfft, no.
噗，没有。
I am a mailman.
我是一名邮递员。
Like the postal oath says,
正如邮政誓言所说，
neither bunions or onions
nor ditches or dangers
既不是拇囊炎也不是洋葱
也没有沟渠或危险
will stop me from giving stuff
to strangers.
会阻止我给予东西
给陌生人。
[applauds]
[鼓掌]
[soft orchestral music]
[轻柔的管弦乐]
[doorbell rings]
[门铃响]
- Ah!
- Special delivery!
- 啊！
- 特别送货！
- Special un-delivery!
- [screams]
- 特别不发货！
- [尖叫]
Oof.
钱币。
Being a mailman isn't like
being Santa Claus at all.
成为一名邮递员并不像
根本就是圣诞老人。
[gasps]
[喘气]
[jingle bells ringing]
[铃儿响叮当]
[straining]
[紧张]
Ho, ho, ho!
Oh!
嗬，嗬，嗬！
哦！
Ooh!
Hey, we're beard bros.
- [growls]
嘿，我们是胡子兄弟。
- [咆哮]
Oh, uh, merry Fishmas!
哦，呃，鱼节快乐！
- It's July!
- Just take a letter.
- 七月了！
- 就拿一封信吧。
- I don't want it!
- Neither bunions or onions!
- 我不想要！
- 既不是拇囊炎也不是洋葱！
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
[screams]
Huh, ooh.
[尖叫声]
呵呵。
Ah.
[screams]
啊。
[尖叫声]
Take your mail!
[grunts]
拿走你的邮件！
[咕哝]
- Hey!
- [grunting]
- 嘿！
- [咕哝]
I'll zip your code so hard!
我会努力压缩你的代码！
Ah!
En garde!
啊!
准备好了！
En lard!
猪油！
- [screaming]
- [尖叫]
- Ho, ha!
- I'm gonna stamp you!
- 嗬，哈！
- 我要给你盖章！
Hi, ha!
- Ha!
嗨，哈！
- 哈！
I'll send you butt express!
我给你寄屁股快递！
[screams]
[尖叫声]
[grunts]
Huh?
[咕哝]
啊？
You can't run
from your civic duties!
你不能跑
来自你的公民义务！
[screaming]
- [screaming]
[尖叫]
- [尖叫]
Oh.
- Ha!
哦。
- 哈！
Get it, slap back,
no take backs!
得到它，拍回来，
没有收回！
[sighs]
[叹气]
[both chuckling]
[两人都笑了]
Not bad.
不错。
This summons is for Bubble Bass,
这个召唤是为了泡泡巴斯，
you nincompoops!
你们这些白痴！
- Hm.
- 嗯。
[bell rings and clatters]
[铃声和叮当声]
- Coming.
- Ah!
- 来了。
- 啊！
- Uh!
- Don't leave!
- 呃！
- 不要离开！
Almost there.
快到了。
- Ha!
- 哈！
Oh, boy, I never get visitors.
哦，天哪，我从来没有接待过访客。
Special delivery
for one special, old man.
特快专递
献给一位特殊的老人。
Uh, uh, mm...
呃呃呃嗯……
I can't find any mail for him.
- Oh, I never get any mail.
我找不到他的任何邮件。
- 哦，我从来没有收到过任何邮件。
[sobbing]
That's so sad.
[抽泣]
太悲伤了。
Let's give him some of
the other mail, huh?
我们给他一些
另一封邮件，嗯？
I found a letter for you,
Old Man Walker.
我找到一封信给你
沃克老人。
[beeping]
[嘟嘟声]
I've been drafted!
Oh, boy!
我已经被征召入伍了！
哦，孩子！
Wow, if one letter
made him this happy,
哇，如果一封信
让他如此幸福，
I bet all of the mail
will make him explode with joy.
我打赌所有的邮件
会让他高兴得爆炸。
[laughs]
[笑]
Sure, wow, all of this for me?
当然，哇，这一切都是为了我？
[explosion]
[爆炸]
[laughter]
[笑声]
What's next, Postman Patrick?
接下来做什么，邮递员帕特里克？
[gulps]
Mm-mm.
[吞咽]
嗯嗯。
[sighs]
We're all out of mail.
[叹气]
我们都没有邮件了。
[engine rumbles]
[发动机隆隆声]
Let's ask that ice cream truck
if it knows
让我们问问那辆冰淇淋车
如果它知道
where to find some mail.
- That's no ice cream truck.
在哪里可以找到一些邮件。
- 那不是冰淇淋车。
It's a mail truck.
- Really?
这是一辆邮车。
- 真的吗？
I thought all trucks were girls.
我以为所有卡车都是女孩。
[laughter]
[笑声]
[tires squeal]
[轮胎吱吱声]
Wow, we hit the postal jackpot!
哇，我们中了邮政大奖了！
Cool.
[engine rumbles]
凉爽的。
[发动机隆隆声]
Huh?
Hey!
啊？
嘿！
Those weirdos stole my truck!
[grunts]
那些怪人偷了我的卡车！
[咕哝]
[sirens blaring]
[警笛鸣响]
Follow those postal pilferers!
追随那些邮政盗窃者！
A special delivery.
特别送货。
Special delivery for Fred!
弗雷德的特别送货！
- Mwah.
- Huh?
- 哇。
- 啊？
[growls]
Who's Carol?
[咆哮]
卡罗尔是谁？
[chuckles]
[笑声]
This one's for you, Penny!
这是给你的，佩妮！
[screaming]
[尖叫]
Huh?
Oh, great.
啊？
哦，太好了。
The raft I ordered
has finally arrived.
我订购的木筏
终于到了。
[screaming]
[尖叫]
[dramatic music]
[戏剧音乐]
♪ ♪
♪♪
[metal clanks]
- Huh?
[金属叮当声]
- 啊？
Pirates!
海盗！
- Wha...?
- 世界卫生大会...？
[both growling]
[双方咆哮]
Why are these pirates
dressed like mail people?
为什么这些海盗
穿得像邮递员？
- They want to steal our mail!
- Repel the boarders!
- 他们想偷我们的邮件！
- 击退寄宿生！
Repelling boarders, sir!
排斥寄宿生，先生！
- Ugh!
- Harold!
- 呃！
- 哈罗德！
No!
不！
I'm shipping these COD.
我正在运送这些货到付款。
Crash on delivery.
交货时崩溃。
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
Eeh, oh.
And here comes some air mail.
呃，哦。
一些航空邮件来了。
[retches]
[干呕]
[screaming]
[尖叫]
Huh?
啊？
Another jury summons
for Bubble Bass.
另一个陪审团传票
对于泡泡低音。
Special delivery!
特别发货！
Oh, all we have left
is junk mail!
哦，我们只剩下一切了
是垃圾邮件！
Don't worry.
不用担心。
They'll never find us
in this post office.
他们永远找不到我们
在这个邮局。
♪ ♪
♪♪
[sighs]
[doorbell rings]
[叹气]
[门铃响]
Here's today's mail, warden.
这是今天的邮件，典狱长。
[together]
Special delivery.
[一起]
特别送货。
[both chuckle]
[两人都笑了]